mybookmarkingsite.com 2017-09-21

# I.

Terms and Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it, this page hereby stipulates how
we meet this commitment.
Our Terms
I.      Affiliated Links
Due to this Website’s affiliations with numerous companies, which it had a prior agreement to
place their ads and web links, hereby reserves its rights when these ad server affiliations gather
certain information deemed necessary as a consequence of your visit to this Website.
Nevertheless, kindly take caution every time you click on these ads or web links since you will
be redirected to a new website. Therefore, we advise that you always take time to read
carefully and fully understand these new websites’ privacy policies as well as their site’s user
terms to prevent yourself from unanticipated issues.
II.     Purchases
In case you make a purchase or purchases from any of the company sites that our Website
represents, said company site thereby collects personal information from you such as your full
name, valid email address, contact number, shipping and/or billing address, and such other
payment information like your credit card number, credit account name, credit card security
code and card’s expiration date. Our Website or its staff has no obligation to any of your actions
and the other company site’s terms and privacy policies. Therefore, it is important that you
read their terms and privacy policies before filling up their purchase form.

Privacy Policy
I.       Personal Data Protection
     1. The User warrants that it has the legal right to disclose all Personal Data that it does in
         fact disclose to us, and that the processing of that Personal Data (by us) for the
         purposes of responding to your query will not breach any applicable laws.
     2. We warrant that:
             (a) information collected will only be used to respond to your requests for our
                 services;
             (b) it will act only on instructions from the User in relation to the processing of any
                 Personal Data that we collect; and
             (c) appropriate security measures (both technical and organizational) against
                 unlawful or unauthorized processing of Personal Data are in place.
II.      Non-Personal Identifiable Information
Third party companies may set cookies for web analytics purposes, this can track traffic and
traffic sources and monitor their activities.
Our website primarily uses activity log files in obtaining user’s IP address, ISP, browser type exit
logs, date and time logs and other session information necessary to evaluate user’s website
activity, manage significance of content, and diagnose and resolve service or technical issues.
III.     Information Disclosure
We reserve the right to disclose personal information when it believes it is appropriate to
comply with the law, or in response to a subpoena or a court order. This may include
exchanging information with other companies for protection against fraud.
Changes to this Policy
We reserve the right to modify these Terms and Privacy Policy from time to time as we may
deem necessary or as may be required by the law.
